price-hunt.com 2015-12-12

# Privacy Policy at Price-hunt.com

## Privacy Policy

Please read our privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. This privacy policy sets out how Price-Hunt.com uses and protects any information that you give Price-Hunt.com when using this website. We are committed ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

##### Information Collected by Us

We collect and use information about you from various sources. The amount and nature of the information collected and used varies from transaction to transaction as : Information from you - Information you provide to us on applications, other forms, and by other means, such as your name, e-mail ID, and contact numbers. We may collect “Non-Personal Information” – information that cannot be used to identify you – via Cookies, even if you have not registered with or provided any Personal Information to Price-Hunt. Third parties may use Non-Personal Information in order to display advertising that reflects the interests and preferences of our user community. We will not share your personally identifiable information to any third parties and is kept secure.

##### Payments

After choosing your product, you will be directed to the merchant's or service provider's website (such as by following a link from the Websites to the merchant's or service provider's website) or the merchant or service provider will contact you. Any transaction, application or other interaction between you and the merchant or service provider on or through the merchant’s or service provider’s website, offline store or application process will be pursuant to any terms or agreements made available by such merchant or service provider.

##### Links to external websites

This website may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that Price-Hunt.com does not have any control over the other website. Therefore, Price-Hunt.com cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.

##### Children’s Privacy

Protecting the privacy of every minor is equally important to us. The Website is not structured to attract minor children under eighteen (18) years and you hereby acknowledge that you are above the age of eighteen (18) years while using the Website.

##### Changes to our Privacy Policy

Price-Hunt.com may change this policy from time to time without prior notice.If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page. You are requested to check this section of this Website regularly. Upon updating the Privacy Policy, we may revise the "Updated" date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy.
